In the entertainment industry, there's nothing that I can do.
So you don't want to know who ruined your audition.
Someday,
you're gonna have to beg me first.
The president chose Sunny for another reason.
Beyond what was appropriate.
The reason why it has to be Sunny
was because the sponsor asked for him.
Damn it.
Get rid of him.
7 years ago
Thank you for giving me a chance.
I promise that I will do my best here.
I want us to walk one step at a time.
There are no shortcuts in this industry.
Get it done.
Yes, sir.
Is this your first time seeing
the footage of this situation?
It is.
And besides this picture,
there are messages as well, right??
It's a threatening message to prevent you from telling the truth, right?
All right, viewers at home,
we also have an interview video of Mr. Kongkiat
which is the CEO of Dream Entertainment.
The agency representing the artist involved in
the wrongdoing in this incident.
The infamous artist that we’re talking about
is PEN-NUENG.
From the news that an artist from your company has
recklessly caused the car accident, resulting in injuries.
Do you have anything to say about the news?
Sir, Has the victim requested any compensation
or damages at this point?
As for now, I still haven’t heard of anything just yet.
Although if it really happened
then we will have to check first
who exactly has helped PEN-NUENG cover up the incident.
Given then it really happened
exactly according to the news.
You have my words that
we will take the strictest possible action possible.
But we have footage of the car crash,
are you going to deny or act responsible for that?
I'll give you another interview later.
Thank you very much.
But Mr. Kongkiat
All of PEN-NUENG's brand ambassador contracts have been terminated.
His series was also postponed indefinitely.
The hashtag has also been trending for two days straight.
It's not looking good for him.
In the interview, Kongkiat said someone might cover up the incident for PEN-NUENG,
did he imply that it’s Director Arthur?
Director Arthur and PEN-NUENG
They attended college together in America.
There are pictures of them having meals and hanging out together.
Which isn't surprising if Director Arthur
would help his friend at times like this.
Do you also think that Director Arthur did that?
If not, how can PEN-NUENG survive for three years,
with him clearly in a video like that?
But they couldn't cover it up now.
I really wonder who it is.
Who surfaced the video?
I’m beyond curious.
I think that person must be close to PEN-NUENG.
Now I can't think of anyone other than Director Arthur.
He could be the person who tried to cover up and also leaked the video.
If he did that,
what’s in it for him?
Well, that's why I can't think of any other reason.
Did Director Arthur get suspended, right?
If he can’t come up with anything, then they might have to fire him.
Mostly when they ended in such a sensitive situation like this one,
they will no longer be needed.
You know the saying one rotten apple spoils the whole barrel.
Where is he now?
It’s my phone.
Hello?
I'll hurry and get to it.
Do you miss me?
I’m not insane enough to miss you,
we just met the other day.
Get back.
Don't miss me?
But slept at my front door?
It doesn’t make any sense.
Just tell me that you miss me.
Shit!
Why do you always assume things?
I came because I wanted to talk to you.
I don't care why you came,
the only thing I care about is
Do you miss me?
I've never had to sit outside anyone's room before,
only to end up in a situation like this.
Never?
So that was your first time,
waiting outside a man's room.
It’s my honour to be your first.
Get off me!
What are you going to do?
Keep it in.
The longer you hold it,
the harder it is to keep it in.
Just say it.
You did not help PEN-NUENG cover things up,  did you?
What do you think?
From what I know of you,
you're not that kind of person.
The person who called me just now is Game.
The game found that the information had leaked from the company's computer.
The account was used to release the data has just been registered.
Do you wanna know
whose e-mail is it?
It’s your manager’s Email.
Are you serious? P’Kajorn?
That’s impossible.
Where would he get the information from?
And another thing,
He was on the filming set with me and Sky every day.
Are you sure
that he was with you the whole time?
He could have come to the office while you were filming.
I'll be right back.
He might be behind all this, but he just isn’t very smart.
If this gets to the board,
your manager will be fired.
Because it damages the company.
But I believe that he didn't do it.
It doesn’t matter what you believe.
The only thing that matters is
It's about what you make people believe.
You don't have much time
to prove that your manager is innocent.
My car is not parked this way.
I can go by myself.
One more thing,
you shouldn't show up at the company right now.
Why?
I can go anywhere. It's my business.
Or are you just shy,
to have such a handsome guy drive you sports car to the company.
And yet again with assuming stuff.
Didn't you say it yourself
that I don't have much time to save P’Kajorn?
So don't waste my time.
If you don’t let me drop you off,
then I won’t let you go anywhere.
Well If you want to drop me off then follow.
How is it?
Riding a bus for the first time.
Why do you think this was my first?
People like you probably don't like sharing anything with anyone.
You’re right.
I don't like sharing anything with anyone.
So I’m curious to know
Who topped you that day?
So can you just tell me?
How do you get to that?
Get away.
And another thing,
And another thing, I'm not yours.
Who told you this is my first time on a bus?
used to take the bus when I lived in New York.
Bus fare, please.
For your ride back.
Back?
How?
Didn't you say you'd taken the bus before?
You don’t know how to do anything, do you?
I came all this way just to drop you off,
and you’re returning the favor by nagging me?
I didn't ask you to come.
Now I get it.
What do you mean?
It's crowded,
so you can’t really yell at me.
Not like when it's just the two of us.
Do you want me to yell at you now?
Do it then.
Yell at me so the whole bus can hear you.
It’s quite exciting, isn’t it?
We’re arriving soon.
Wait.
A key card to my room.
So you don't have to sleep in front of my room again.
I want to get down now.
Did we just pass the bus stop?
Right there, the stop.
Did he just give him the key card?
We’re here.
Thank you.
Let’s go.
It’s rumoured that
you are the one who leaked the information about PEN-NUENG.
Huh?
Is this true?
Yes, it is.
I didn't do it.
I don't even know him personally.
Who am I to have all that information?
And the reason that I came to the office when you guys were out.
Because I just wanted to take care of my paperwork as usual.
It’s how I always get the job done.
I know, and I believe you.
Although you have to prove that you didn't do it.
Let’s report. Report to the police, so that they can investigate on this.
I assure you that I am innocent. I didn’t do it.
If you wait for the police to help you,
until they take this to court and, all the process is done.
How are you going to earn money in between?
I think that before you could do anything,
they probably would have fired you by then.
Oh shit, you’re right.
What am I supposed to do?
What do I have to do?
Ow!
I’m so screwed.
Why does it have to always be me?
What if you could become a new manager of PEN-NEUNG?
If he let you work as his manager,
so he must be confident
that you didn’t leak any information.
And it will overrule your allegations.
I mean, I understand what you're saying.
But I don't think it's a good idea.
It's not something that people like me can do, you know?
I believe in you.
I believe that you can do it.
If you really think so,
I need a little courage from you guys.
Alright.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I don’t think we can go inside without permission from the room owner.
Wait a moment, let me think about this.
Hey, why didn’t we figure it out before that couldn't possibly get into the building.
Hold on.
Hey!
Where are you going?
I'm sorry.
Are you insane?
Let’s go.
I ask for your help, but not like this.
Hey, this is just so wrong.
I don't think he's in there.
We should come here again next time.
It’s already fuck up enough that you stole a key card,
don’t make things any worse. I’m begging you.
Just do it my way.
I’m just prying the door open.
Whoa.
You've been through a lot, haven't you?
Didn’t you say that you believe in me?
Who the hell are you guys?
Uh, yeah, hi, I’m Kajorn.
I'm an artist manager at Dream Entertainment.
We've had the opportunity to meet before. Wait a moment.
Now I know the situation that you're facing.
And if you want to fix the situation,
you need to let me in and to talk to you.
Just go back.
Hey, you don't just understand what I said, do you?
I just wanted to say what your fans need now
is to hear the truth from you.
The truth?
The truth is, I even pay them monthly.
What more do they want from me?
You guys really go back. I have nothing left to say.
Hey, are you dense?
If you’re not considering doing anything now.
Your career won't be salvageable after this.
Won't be salvageable?
Just go now.
If you don't go,
I'll get the police to drag you out.
Get out of here.
You have to let me in.
I told you to go back.
And don't ever come back here again.
I’m telling you that I’m your only way out.
Are you okay?
Oh, I can't move.
So you're only tough when it comes to picking on old people, huh?
Oh my gosh, at my age things are not the same as they once were.
Do you want me to take you to the doctor?
It's okay. Things were worse than this when I was younger.
But I can only assume that you’ve been worse, right?
Hey, have a look.
PEN-NUENG is…
Your phone is all broken. I can read nothing.
I'll use mine, instead.
What my fans want the most is
simply the truth.
I know what I did was unforgivable, but I want to apologize.
And ask everyone for a chance.
Hey, what a surprise.
I didn't think he would apologize so soon.
And do you think people will forgive him?
You’ll just have to wait and see, right?
Sun, don't turn around.
Oh!
There it is.
Don’t forget to throw in the trash
after you’re done, okay?
Is this your way of giving it back to him?
Everyone, there's breaking news.
A video has surfaced allegedly showing PEN-NUENG,
a celebrity from Dream Entertainment who has been making headlines recently,
hitting someone with his car.
The victim was reportedly left permanently unable to walk.
According to the footage, PEN-NUENG then allegedly drove away
without even getting out to check on the victim.
Even, he has now been issued an apology statement,
but the comments are still in the same direction,
saying that it looks insincere.
And moreover, the sponsors have backed off from all of his projects.
Also he has been removed from all upcoming acting projects.
Yes.
I feel that I have become more myself through this character.
Because Chanont is such a responsible character,
and always try to make the right thing.
He’s like another version of me.
How embarrassing!
Oh, his real life is not as good as he was the drama.
So you see now?
Both the sponsorship and the series has ben canceled.
Please follow our channel and I will keep you guys posted.
Who is it?
Hello?
When are you going to schedule for your nude photoshoot?
Huh?
What?
Nude photos that we agreed on.
Wait a minute.
Whose number did Kajorn give me?
I think he gave you the wrong number.
This is Sky.
Not P’Sun.
Damn it.
Then would you tell Sun that I'm free this evening,
If he is available too, come to my studio.
You’re here as we agreed on.
Are you ready for your nude photoshoot?
What do I have to do?
You just simply need to take everything off.
Cover yourself up with this.
And follow me.
Very beautiful,
and it doesn’t look too revealing as well.
I view them as arts.
Who’s in this picture?
The person who almost made me quit photography.
It calls itself a teacher.
Although what it does is not just teaching,
but it disparages someone else's work
It was once said in front of me that
I will never be succeed.
What is he looking at?
My national award-winning photograph.
I don't know the real reason you're afraid of cameras
but there's one thing I want to tell you.
Seeing someone who once hurt you,
see how successful you've become
is so damn satisfying.
I just couldn't resist taking this photo.
Can you imagine?
Imagine the face of the person who made you afraid of the camera,
see you on the Billboard all over Bangkok.
Like he couldn’t escape you.
How satisfying would that be?
Kongkiat is trying to get rid of you, right?
Are you worried about me?
Theemeka,
You’re acting like this again.
Why?
Are you feeling guilty
for causing the death of your own family?
You’re trying to pay for what you did
to the point where you won't let yourself be happy.
Enough!
You've been dwelling on your mistakes so much
that you haven't faced who you are for the past five years.
Because of this, that’s why you don’t know how to cry.
Don't try to deny it.
That you don't feel anything for me.
Stop being a narcissistic.
I know.
But I'm sure you can feel it
that even right now
my heart is calling out for you.
From now on, you just need to think about me, alright?
The light from the outside is too bright.
Yes, I put the curtain here, it will get softer and then take it from far.
Yeah, okay.
Hello.
- Hello.
Hi, there.
Hello.
Oh, are you setting up?
Yes.
Today, if there's anything for me to help that relates to Sky,
you can contact me immediately.
Alright.
Okay.
Ya, can you take Sky to get dress.
Yes.
That way.
P’Kajorn,
you don’t have to wait here, you know.
I know that you have things to deal with.
I have P’Sun with me. Don't worry.
Gosh, it's okay.
Any other issues, I'll figure things out tomorrow.
I'm here with you today.
You just need to focus on acting.
I'm going to focus on the food at catering area.
It's locked
Why won't it open?
So what do we do now? Do we wait or not?
Hello.
Karn, I called both Em and his manager's number,
but no one’s answering.
Oh, they’re calling me now.
Uh, where are you?
Huh?
Just woke up.
What? We literally catered this to your schedule since you said yours is packed.
Busy?
You’re the only one in this world who’s busy?
We’re really busy too.
Karn,
he just woke up.
What should we do?
If you're very busy, you probably can't come.
Your job here is done.
What should we do? Should we call it off?
- Should we just cancel?
- I don’t know.
P'Karn, should we call it off?
And then we can find a new casting later.
We don’t have that much time.
There's no other way?
The script is very long too.
Ow!
We won't make it in time.
Sun.
Yes?
Can you play as Danai? The role that you auditioned for.
Huh?
Go.
Dress him up.
Right this way, please.
Please inside.
I'll show you the hairdresser.
Go ahead.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Okay, we can use the same costume.
P’Kajorn, Can we discuss the schedule for a bit?
Oh, yeah.
But would it be good?
Because you said that Sun was not ready.
When I said that he’s not ready yet, I meant in terms of acting experience.
I can see that Sun felt kinda similar to this character, so I’ll let him try it out.
Of course.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll handle his schedule.
Yes, thank you very much.
Let’s go.
How is it, Sun? Can you wear it?
Let me see.
A little uncomfortable, I think.
Really?
Wow!
Okay, slay.
Is this really a burned-out office worker
who decided to take his own life in the end?
You look so cool. Why on earth would you consider doing that?
I think P'Karn, she probably saw something in you.
That’s why she chose P'Sun to play this role.
You can do it.
Don't worry, alright?
Nong Sky, come to the filming set now.
Yes.
- Come on, come on.
- P’Sun, don't forget the relaxation exercise that I taught you.
Breathe in, breathe out, fighting!
He’s on his way.
Come here, touch up a bit.
Please.
Have a seat and wait right here.
What is the capital city of Lithuania?
Come to tell me the answer in the restroom.
Why are you here?
Hey, wait.
- Why are you…
- Do it.
You can play victim all you want.
It’s fine.
If that makes you feel better.
If you think you’re in this situation
because I forced you into it.
You don't want this to go any further, do you?
But if you want,
ask me for it.
What?
You need to think about what you really want.
This is a public restroom.
You don't want me to back off, do you?
Are you going to ignore your needs again?
Why do you have to make everything a puzzle?
That's so annoying.
I understand you.
What do you want?
Why don't you try asking me for it?
Or are you afraid of the truth?
I’m not known to be afraid of anything.
I never go easy on anyone.
I’ll let you know that
I'm a guy who doesn't hesitate at all,
If I have to break something,
to own it completely.
Sorry, is anyone in here?
Is anyone there?
You and your manager
might need this.
Director Arthur.
I can’t hold it in anymore.
What are you guys doing so slowly?
P’Sun, you can do it.
Ready?
Yes, I am.
Don't get nervous.
Just act like how you feel.
Here.
Could you have a look at this for me?
I'll get going.
Okay. I'll go check on him over there first.
Yeah.
The sky is so beautiful today.
How is a beautiful sky related to a suicide scene?
I don't know, just the color scheme is simple and easy on the eyes.
If you see the sky like this for the last time,
isn't that supposed to mean something?
How about this, I’ll let you play this part as you imagined first.
Ever imagined the last second before dying?
I did.
Normally, before anyone dies like this
they often act hesitantly or mutter to themself.
Some people will take off their shoes to convey freedom from the planet,
or they might call someone.
Or even stare at the sky before suicide?
You get the gist, right?
Wanna rehearse?
It's okay. I’m going to do it.
Suicide can only be done once.
If practicing, I'm afraid I'll be so familiar that it doesn’t look realistic.
I walk to the edge of the building
which is my goal today.
What had to be done,
I've done it all.
Now I can end my life.
Cut!
Hey, save him. Get him out. Be careful.
Get him out.
Be careful.
How are you, Sun? Okay?
I’m fine.
Do you want another round?
Uh, P'Karn, do you want another take?
No, it’s good we can move on.
Okay.
We got it.
Passed.
Yay!
Come on, come on.
Let’ continue, scene five, take three.
P’Sun
You gave me goosebumps.
I felt you were going to do it for real.
I felt like
you were going to leave me for goods.
Really?
I didn’t know that.
P’Kajorn,
Yes?
When's his next shoot with me?
I think in two days.
Then I'll postpone it a little longer.
Hello, sir.
Hello, there.
Long time no see
You may have a seat.
I want to change the content of the script
as contacted in advance.
Because you're the funder of this project
so I wanted to talk to you first.
Which part do you want to change?
Danai’s character that plays by Sun
When I saw his performance,
I just wanted to adjust the ending chapter a little bit.
This character has a line saying that
“There's no point in living.
But still I don't want to die
so I have to continue to live.”
And then...
“This life means nothing.”
Is that right?
P’Kajorn, what are you doing here?
Uh, do you know each other?
Yes, we do
Then I'll be excused.
Can I go in and talk to PEN-NUENG
He’s not in a good mood right now.
I think you should go back first.
I don’t think so.
How can I leave him with the manager who leaked his video?
What are you saying?
I'm not just saying that but I also have proof.
Whatever you talked to Kongkiat at Alice’s I heard it all.
Didn’t you tell me if I say sorry and things will get better?
Didn't you say this was my last resort?
See?
Look at me now.
I lost everything.
There's nothing left.
I shouldn’t ever believe anything that you said.
You too.
I told you, right?
Don't let anyone in.
Why did you let him in?
You're really stupid.
Stupid from day one
until today.
You never even got better.
I get it now.
Phu must have really lost all patience with you.
You really ripped into Phu, didn't you?
And you treated the victim so carelessly after the accident.
I’m not surprised that Phu gave that video to
Kongkiat.
You did that?
Did you?
Why did you do that?
PEN-NUENG!
It’s because you’re being like this.
Where are you going?
Where do you think you’re going?
You can leave too.
I want to be left alone.
I know a brand owner.
I just went to talk to him yesterday.
He said that
he still wants to work with you.
He just wants
you sincerely apologize to the victim and the public at a press conference.
What brand?
Micro Hertz.
It’s just a small brand.
It's just a small brand, but it's a small step for you to get up again.
I know you've had more before
but now you seem to have only two options.
First, put your ego aside and start over.
Or keep being egotistic and let everything collapse right in front of you.
So, are you ready to start over with me?
This is for you.
I want to apologize to everyone
for taking so long to address this publicly.
I admit that what I did
was wrong.
My mistake left her father disabled.
I promise you guys that
I will take responsibility for my actions.
And I will fully cooperate with the legal process.
About the rumour that
my friend who’s executive director at Dreams
has helped me cover this up,
I want to tell you here that's not true.
Everything is my decision.
You’re not that stupid,
Mr. Two baht.
You finally agree to meet me,
Director Arthur.
Right.
Although it’s not for good reasons.
I had the IT department checked
on who leaked PEN-NUENG's data from the company's computers
Found out that the account that leaked that information
belongs to Kajorn.
Oh, really?
Why did he do that?
He deliberately hurt P’PEN-NUENG and our companies.
But the IP address
traces back to the computer that released the data,
and it was logged in using your password, Sunny.
I think it's a misunderstanding.
Maybe I logged into the company's computer.
But I think it's for my personal work.
I have proof of everything.
Both the video from CCTV
and the time that you used that computer.
So I can only assume that
Kongkiat must give you this information.
So that you can get rid of PEN-NUENG out of your way.
So you’ve tried to kill two birds with one stone.
And tried to get rid of Kajorn as well.
You’re so smart.
You seem to know it all.
That’s why everyone wants you as a backer.
You know? knowing too much isn’t a good thing.
You know who my backer is.
It seems like you don't want to please me no more?
The reason I wanted to approach you,
it’s just that I just want a connection from you.
But right now I don’t think you’re necessary anymore.
Because no matter what The leading role in the Memory the series
is mine anyway.
Without any competitor.
Are you sure?
You're probably used to people approaching you,
but someday,
You could be the one who came to me.
How did you know I was here?
Or do you want to hear that answer from me?
Seriously, I can just tell you that
What do you really want?
Why don’t you try to enlighten me then.
What exactly that I want?
Instead of getting answer from others,
Why don't you try asking yourself first?
I don’t care if you’re not telling.
I came because I wanted to talk to you.
Whatever the situation is now,
in the end
I’m the winner.
You don't believe it, right?
Hello?
Please tell Kongkiat,
I'm handing over the decision-making authority for The Memory to him.
As a Dream board member.
What the hell are you doing?
At this point,
you still don't accept it?
That you like me.
The sound of your heart
beats so loudly, it hurts my ears.
I know.
But if I accepted, what could it change?
So, how's it feel? Feeling your heart pound
so hard you wanna die?
It might be frustrating.
But not to the point that you can’t live with it.
Do you know why?
Because you want to live.
Deep down,
you still want to live.
This is the chapter that I adjusted.
The scene that we're going to shoot may change a little.
Try reading to understand the character first.
Ready?
You can just literally read it out.
Just because I’m not dead yet,
so I only have to live.
Whether the goal in life,
or the meaning of life
I never had it.
Sometimes.
So I couldn't help but question myself
that do I need to keep living my life
just for the reason that
I’m still breathing?
Why?
The script that you changed. I feel like…
There's a little different feeling.
You have such a good sense.
Yes, the second half
it was adjusted because I went and asked for advice.
So I just changed it.
Doesn't it feel like it's a little different from the old script interpretation?
Well, Sun might feel like it's different,
but I feel like the two of them are similar.
Who are you talking about?
Director Arthur.
i talked to him and listened to him,
So I made a few adjustments.
Just because I'm not dead yet,
So I have to live my life.
Whether the goal in life,
or the meaning of life,
I never had it.
I’ve never understood the joy
that other people experience.
I don't understand why
people can smile and be happy.
It makes me question myself.
Do I need to keep living
just because I’m still breathing?
By living
without being able to feel anything,
is a deathly torture.
That means
suffering like this
is the price I have to pay
to keep me alive.
I think
there are only people who want to live
that needs a reason to be alive.
Even if you suffer,
Try to look for something around you that makes you smile,
and be thankful for it.
If it's someone who can feel love
even for just a little.
Then you…
have the right to have
the reason to be alive.
People whose hearts are not dead yet,
deserves to live on.
Please, can you make me cry?
Ahh!
Why?
You look like
you just figured something out.
Remember what you asked me?
What did I ask you?
Do I believe in karma?
I replied that I believe in the idea of karma.
If we were meant to share karma together,
we will meet again.
Just like the two of us now
But I do believe the karma is real.
Wait a minute.
You are…
The official press event for The Memory the series.
Why don’t we know any of this?
Why don’t you just leave the Deam Company?
For the safety of those around you.
If you’re going to hold a grudge,
blame yourself instead.
You will put people around you in trouble too.
What are you going to do?
I’m here now,
you guys can let him go.